<resources>
    <string name="app_name">P.Shiksha 4.0</string>
    <string name="login_success">Login Successful</string>
    <string name="login_failed">Login Failed</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection">Please check your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="otp_sent_success">OTP sent successfully to phone number</string>
    <string name="otp_sent_failed">Failed to send OTP. Please check your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="otp_incorrect">Make sure OTP entered is correct.</string>
    <string name="invalid_phone_number">Please enter a valid phone Number.</string>
    <string name="user_profile_success">Information saved.</string>
    <string name="user_profile_failed">An error occurred. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong">Something went Wrong. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="ed_sheet">ED Sheet</string>
    <string name="ed_sheet_desc">As Michael Harvey writes, paragraphs are “in essence—a form of punctuation, and like other forms of punctuation they are meant to make written material easy to read.”[1] Effective paragraphs are the fundamental units of academic writing; consequently, the thoughtful, multifaceted arguments that your professors expect depend on them. Without good paragraphs, you simply cannot clearly convey sequential points and their relationships to one another.

                                 \nMany novice writers tend to make a sharp distinction between content and style, thinking that a paper can be strong in one and weak in the other, but focusing on organization shows how content and style converge in deliberative academic writing. Your professors will view even the most elegant prose as rambling and tedious if there isn’t a careful, coherent argument to give the text meaning. Paragraphs are the “stuff ” of academic writing and, thus, worth our attention here.</string>
    <string name="check_out">Check Out</string>


    <string-array name="college_names">
        <item>NSUT</item>
        <item>DTU</item>
        <item>IGTU</item>
        <item>IIT</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="college_degree">
        <item>B.Tech</item>
        <item>M.Tech</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="college_branch">
        <item>Computer Science</item>
        <item>EE</item>
        <item>ICE</item>
        <item>ICEICE</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="college_graduation_year">
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2021</item>
        <item>2022</item>
        <item>2023</item>
        <item>2024</item>
        <item>2025</item>
        <item>2026</item>
        <item>2027</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>